

#### **Contact**

E-mail:

konrad.lewandowski92@gmail.com GitHub:

https://github.com/KonradLewandowski

Phone:

**+48 666 960 130**Date of birth:

04.11.1992

City:

Gdańsk

## **Good programming skills:**

HTML&CSS | JavaScript | Node | Express | Pug.js

## **Knowledge of:**

MongoDB | Firebase | PostrgeSQL | REST | Git | Gulp | SASS

#### **Basic knowledge of:**

React | Hooks | Redux

### Languages

English – **B2**Polish - **native** 

### Konrad Lewandowski

I am a former soldier with a seven year history of military service.

Over the years I have acquired many traits that have shaped me to be a. Immunity to stress, determination in goal achievement, professionalism and availability are only few of my positive qualities. For the past year I have focused on building and expanding my skills in the field of web development. Front-end, back-end, data bases and external API's are some of the topics I have made myself familiar with. I would gladly become a part of a team of developers, from whom I can learn and further expand my abilities while working to achieve common objectives.

## My projects(programming experience):

## Recipes app

Downloading data from the server (a list of recipes) and displaying them in the front-end layer The possibility to send a recipe to the server using the 'GET' method (REST API) Sent recipes are automatically assigned to the user Adding/deleting recipes from bookmarks.

Used technologies: HTML&CSS | JavaScript | API | Parcel

#GitHub: github.com/KonradLewandowski/recipies-app-project.git

**#YouTube**: <u>youtu.be/QipPqK00w-4</u> **#Netlify**: recipies-app-kl.netlify.app

### Calories calculator

Create a new user, log in and log out with the JWT authentication. Resetting the password via a link sent by email. Adding a new product and searching an existing in the database. Manipulating user data. Store user's data on the server.

Used technologies: HTML&CSS | JavaScript | Pug.js | Node | Express

| MongoDB | Mongoose | Nodemailer | Parcel

#GitHub: github.com/KonradLewandowski/calories-calculator.git

#YouTube: youtu.be/xXfNezI8pdM

#Heroku: calories-calculator-konrad.herokuapp.com

#### Map app

Getting user's geolocation and displaying on the map. Possibility to create a mark, and store locally. It works with external API.

Used technologies: **HTML&CSS** | **JavaScript** | **API** | **Leaflet** 

#GitHub: github.com/KonradLewandowski/map-workout-app.git

**#YouTube**: <u>youtu.be/IrGDF5o0JYM</u> **#Netlify**: <u>https://map-app-kl.netlify.app</u>

## Additional courses

- Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More 2022 Udemy
- The Complete JavaScript Course 2022 Udemy
- Programowanie w JavaScript od Zera do Mastera -Udemy

## Work experience

07.2015 - 06.2022 [7 years.]

Professional soldier / 25th air cavalry brigade / Tomaszów Mazowiecki

- Availability and flexibility,
- Dutiful approach to assigned tasks,
- Supervision and guidance of younger members of the team,
- Planning, organising and performing group operations.

07.2013 – 12.2014 [1 year 6 months.]

Production line operator / Uzdrowisko Wieniec / Wieniec-Zdrój

- Maintenance on the production line,
- Machines configuration.

## Education

09.2008 – 06.2012 ZSM Jozef Pilsudski in Radziejów I**T technician** 

# Hobby

- parachuting,
- astrophysics.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).